Guide to the Service Employees International Union Local 585 Records, 1966-1989 AIS.1982.14
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Collection Additions, II.
  - SEIU - Contract Surveys, 1981-1983 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - SEIU - Internal Research - Financial Statistics and Company Information, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - SEIU - Convention Materials - Programs/Newsletters, 1972-1981 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - GPS Investors Company - Contract - Working Copy, 1975-1977 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - GPS Investors Company - Contract - Signed, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Butler County - Sunnyview Nursing Home - Contract Negotiations - Working Copy, 1972-1980 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - GPS Investors Company - Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Jefferson Dubois Vo-Tech - Contract Agreements - Working Copy, 1972-1981 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Jefferson Dubois Vo-Tech - Correspondence and Contract Agreements, 1975-1982 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Jefferson-Morgan School District - Employees Dues, Grievances, Awards, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Kiski Area School District - Correspondence with SEIU, 1979-1980 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Leechburg - Contract Negotiations and Agreement - Working Copy, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Mt. Lebanon School District - Secretaries - Contract Negotiations and Agreements - Working Copy, 1978-1981 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Mt. Lebanon School District - Cafeteria - Contract Agreement, Mailing List, Letters, 1980-1983 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Mt. Lebanon School District - Guards - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Mt. Lebanon School District - Contract Negotiations and Agreement - Working Copy, 1976-1980 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Mt. Lebanon School District - Contract Negotiations and Agreements - Working Copy, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Hopewell Township - Contract Agreements - Working Copy, 1974-1977 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Hopewell Township School - Guards Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Hopewell Township School - Secretaries - Contract Negotiations and Agreements - Working Copy, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Sunnyview Nursing Home - Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - National Industry Pension Fund, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Collective Bargaining Registration, 1970-1974 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Gallatin National Bank Building - Contract - Old, 1967, 1970, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Greene County Memorial Hospital - Contract - Signed, 1975-1977 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Greene County Memorial Hospital - Contract Agreement - Old, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Evergreen Nursing Home - Contract Agreement - Signed, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Lafayette Manor - Contract Agreement, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Mountain View - Contract Agreement, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Monsour Medical Center - Contract - Signed, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Mountain View Medical Facilities - Contract Agreement - Signed, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Jeannette Hospital - Materials Dealing with Labor Cases, 1971-1974 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Election Materials, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Bargaining Information - Wage Proposals, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Monsour Hospital - Gale Ridnour Grievance, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Monsour Hospital - Pearl DaPra Grievance, 1981-1983 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Monsour Hospital - Pearl DaPra Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Frick Memorial Hospital - Layoff Arbitration - Community Petitions, 1983-1984 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Monsour Hospital - Helen Dunn Grievance, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - LRNAP Convention - By-Laws, Letters, Notices, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - LRNAP - Budget, Reports, Balance Sheet, Notices, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - LRNAP - Reports Notices, Letters, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - LRNAP - Convention Materials - Reports, Notices, Letters, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Monsour Hospital - Joan Gillispie - Unfair Labor Case, 1975-1976 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Andrew Rusbarski Life Insurance Grievance - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Monsour Hospital - William Opalsky Discharge, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Washington County Health Center - Contract Negotiations and Agreements, 1977-1981 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Wage Negotiations and Salary Projection, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Monsour Hospital - Monsour Medical Foundation 10th-14th, 16th Annual Ball - Programs (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Dues Check-Off, March-September 1973 (Box 70, Folder 1-4)
  - Albert Gallatin School District - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Brownsville School District - Correspondence and Grievances, 1977-1980 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Blairsville-Saltsburg - Contract Negotiations and Agreements - Old, 1977-1980 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Frick Rally - Letters, Notices, Newspaper Clippings, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Fayette Vo-Tech - Contract Negotiations and Agreements, 1978-1981 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Hopewell Township - Clerical - Contract Agreements, 1979-1981 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Mt. Pleasant School District - Cafeteria - Contract Negotiations and Agreements, 1976-1979 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Penn Trafford School District - Interstate United Cafeteria - Contract Agreements, 1974-1977 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - United School District - Contract Negotiations and Agreements, 1973-1976 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Westmoreland School District - Contract Negotiation and Agreements, 1978-1980 (Box 71, Folder 10-12)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Layoffs, Arbitrations, Letters, News, Agreements, 1977-1984 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - SEIU/AFL-CIO - Convention Materials, 1970-1980 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - SEIU - Labor Research, 1977-1980 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - SEIU - Labor News - Newsletters and Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO - Convention Research, 1977-1981 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO - Presidential and Executive Reports, 1975, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Allegheny County - AFL-CIO Per Capita Tax Dues, 1974-1975 (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
  - Allegheny County - Labor Council - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Armstrong Clarion Counties - Labor Council - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1975-1978 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Armstrong Clarion Counties - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Armstrong County - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Beaver County - Labor Council - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Beaver County - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Blair and Bedford Counties - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1974-1979 (Box 73, Folder 9-11)
  - Butler County - United Labor Council - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1977-1979 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Central Westmoreland County Labor Council - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1974-1979 (Box 73, Folder 13-14)
  - Clearfield County Labor Council - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1974-1978 (Box 73, Folder 15-17)
  - SEIU Local 585 - David Weiss Correspondence, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Eastern Conference of Service Employees - Per Capita Dues, 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Fayette County Labor Council - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1973-1979 (Box 73, Folder 20-22)
  - Johnstown Labor Council - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1976-1979 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Northern Westmoreland County - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1976-1979 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Joint Council Per Capita Forms, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 25-26)
  - Pennsylvania Joint Council #45 - Per Capita Forms, 1975, 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 27-28)
  - PA Joint Council - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1972-1974 (Box 73, Folder 29-30)
  - Pennsylvania AFL-CIO - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1974-1979 (Box 73, Folder 31-33)
  - SEIU/AFL-CIO - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1974-1980 (Box 73, Folder 34-37)
  - Venango County - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1973-1976 (Box 73, Folder 38-39)
  - Venango County Labor Council - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1976-1979 (Box 73, Folder 40)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Council - AFL-CIO - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 41)
  - West Coper - Central Westmoreland Labor Council - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1974-1975 (Box 73, Folder 42)
  - Wilkins Township - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1971-1972 (Box 73, Folder 43)
  - Allegheny County - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1972-1974 (Box 73, Folder 44)
  - Allegheny County - Labor Council - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 45)
  - ACLC - Per Capita Tax Dues (Box 73, Folder 46)
  - Eastern Conference of SEIU - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1976-1978 (Box 73, Folder 47-48)
  - Pennsylvania AFL-CIO - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1971-1977 (Box 73, Folder 49-51)
  - Pennsylvania Joint Council #45 - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 52-53)
  - SEIU - Per Capita Tax Dues, 1970-1977 (Box 73, Folder 54-56)
  - Post Office - Statement of Mailing Matter with Permit Imprints, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 57)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Death Gratuities - Paid - Correspondence and Record, 1972-1975 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Death Gratuities - Pending - Correspondence and Record, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Conference of Service Employees - Per Capita Tax Record, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Johnstown Labor Council - Per Capita Tax Record, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Labor-Management and Welfare Pension - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Melvin Brooks - Memos, Reports, Letters on Tax Filing, 1975-1976 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Misc. Expenses, 1971-1972 (Box 74, Folder 7-8)
  - PSSU Billing - Monthly Records, 1975-1976 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Pacosh - OSHA - Newspaper Clippings, Reports, Newsletters, 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - SEIU - Record of Officer and Employee Pension Funds, 1973, 1975-1976 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - SEIU Local 585 - The Travelers Insurance - Quarterly Billing, 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - AFL-CIO - Union Label & Service Trades Council of Pennsylvania, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Workmen's Compensation, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Labor Research - Bargaining Agreements, Registration, 1973-1979 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - SEIU Local 585 - News - Various Editions, 1973-1975 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - AFL-CIO - Pamphlets/Campaign Information (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - SEIU Local 29 - Department Store Negotiations, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 69 - Constitution and By-Laws, Contract Agreements, SEIU News, Notices, 1965-1975 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - SEIU Local 126 - Contract Agreements, Grievance Cases, and Letters, 1973-1974 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - SEIU Local 188 PGH - List of Officers, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 192-B - Contract Agreement and List of Officers, 1971, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 227 - Correspondence, Grievances, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - SEIU Local 395 - List of Officers, Photographs, Newsletters, 1973-1974 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - SEIU Local 439 - Bethlehem - List of Officers, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - SEIU Local 555 - Contract Agreement, Grievance Cases, News Reports, Letters, 1973-1977 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - SEIU Local 555 - Contract Negotiations and Agreements, 1973-1975 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Local 555 - Constitutions and Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Wage Surveys, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Contract Summaries, 1972-1978 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - SEIU Local 666 - Executive Board Minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - SEIU Local 666 - Grievance Meeting Minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Pennsylvania State Education Association - Contract Agreements, Newspaper Clippings, Notices, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittsburgh - Contract - Signed, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - SEIU/AFL-CIO - Receipts and Disbursement, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - SEIU - Solidarity Day - News Clippings, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence - Merger Information, Notices, Reports, 1981, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - US/Benleaux Young Leaders Conference - Event Information, Schedule, News, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Power to the People - Counter-Inflation Research, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - SEIU 1199 - Leadership Conference - Financial Reports, Research, By-Laws, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - SEIU 1199 - Leadership Conference - Reports/Merger Statement, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Nursing Home Training Institute - Contract Proposal, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - SEIU 1199 - Delegate - Contract and Job Information, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - AFL-CIO - 3rd Biennial Convention - Research, Labor Statistics, Organizing Reports, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Food and Beverage Trade Department - Solidarity Information Kit, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Solidarity Day Stickers, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 11-13)
  - Allegheny County - Training and Employment Board/Associated Community Action Program - Contract, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Conway YMCA - Contract Negotiations and Agreements, 1978-1979 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - COPE - Legislative Activities, 1974-1977 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Local 675 - PESEA - List of Officers, 1974, 1976, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Local 686 - List of Officers, Memos, 1973-1974, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Letters, Addresses of Officers, List of SEIU Arbitration Cases, 1973-1978 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Research Materials, 1972-1975 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Memo - Staff Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Mission Childcare Consortium - Contract Negotiations and Agreement, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - PA Workmen's Compensation - Summary of 1975 Amendments to Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Act (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Proposition 13 - Maps and Assessed Proposed Property Taxes, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Salary Information, List of Employees, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - SEIU - Eastern Conference - Research, Notices, Conference Materials, 1975-1977 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Teledyne Economic Development Company - National Labor Relations Board Case, 1974-1976 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Consolidated Gas Conference - Reports, Notices, Letters, 1975-1977 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - SEIU - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 78, Folder 2-3)
  - Gas Industry - Research Data, 1975-1976 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Greater Washington Area Parks and Recreation - Labor Cases, 1971-1974 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 250 - Grievance Cases, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Alemeda Eligibility Tech - Time Study - Research Reports, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Bay District Joint Council - Contract Agreements, 1974, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - SEIU - International Correspondence - Letters and Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - SEIU - International Mailings - Letters and Reports, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - SEIU - International Scholarships - Letters, Forms, and Reports, 1975-1978 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - International Union Gas Conference - Conference Materials, 1976-1977 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - SEIU - Labor Management Reporting - Letters, Reports, Notes, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Judge Sweet NLRB Court Decisions, 1974-1976 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - SEIU Local 585 - NLRB Court Cases, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - SEIU Local 666 - Contract Agreements, Letters, Notices, Lists of Officers, Grievances, 1972-1978 (Box 78, Folder 16-17)
  - SEIU Local 999 - Grievances, 1974-1976 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - SEIU - Other Unions - Grievances, Letters, Notices, Reports, 1972-1977 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - SEIU - Louis Kushner - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - PED/AFL-CIO - Legislative Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - SEIU - Pennsylvania Locals - List of Officers, 1974-1978 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - SEIU - Publication Requests - Letters, Photographs, Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - SEIU - Report Forms, 1976-1977 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - SEIU - School District Contract Survey - Need Done - Uncompleted Contract (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - SEIU - Union Dues Structures - Newspaper Clippings, Grievance Cases, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - SEIU - Wage and Benefits Surveys, 1970-1975 (Box 78, Folder 27-28)
  - SEIU Local 399 - Contract Agreements, Letters, Notices, 1974-1978 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Building Services, Inc. - Contract Agreements and Legal Notices, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Conway Railroad YMCA - NLRB Cases, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Executive Board Notices, 1972, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - SEIU - Food Stamp Information - Undated Notices (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - SEIU - Government Study Commission - Memorandum Newsletters, Letters, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Grievance Procedures, 1969-1971 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Welfare Trust Fund - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Job Posting Samples - Letters and Notices, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - SEIU Local 163 - Letters, Notices, Grievances, 1969-1983 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 79, Folder 10-11)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Political Endorsement - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Postal Workers Union - Collective Bargaining - Contains Collective Bargaining in the Postal Service: A Ten Year Quest to Gain Equality with Private Economy, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Pennsylvania Social Services Union - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Resolutions, 1973, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Seniority Rosters - Letters, Seniority Lists (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - SEIU - News Releases, 1971-1972 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Financial Records of SEIU Subsidy (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence Pertaining to Sex Discrimination and EEO Issues, 1973-1974 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Stewards - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Stewards Chapter Meetings, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Trust Fund Information, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Unemployment Compensation - Information, 1972-1974 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - SEIU Local 585 - United Way - List of Local 585 Chapter Presidents, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - SEIU Local 585 - YMCA Correspondence, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - SEIU Local 1199 - The Bread & Rose Strike, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Americans for Democratic Action - Fund Raising Report, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Campaign Endorsements, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Children's Lobby - Research Materials, By-Laws, and Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - SEIU - Coalition on Human Needs - Letters, Proposal for Emergency Transportation System, Reports, and News, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - SEIU - Committee On Political Education - Letters, Reports, Memos, Bulletin, AFL-CIO News, 1972-1974 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 585 - George Hardy Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 80, Folder 6-7)
  - SEIU Local 585 - George E. Fairchild Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Collective Bargaining Research - Newsletters, Reports, Research Papers, 1971-1974 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Credit Union Committee - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Local 585 - H.R. 1 Welfare Reform Bill - Letters, Summary, Reports, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Legal Suggestions - Pamphlets, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - SEIU/AFL-CIO - Newsletters, 1972-1974 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence with State Legislation, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 14-15)
  - SEIU Local 585 - PA Maintenance & Trades Materials - Letters, Newspaper Clippings, and Reports (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - SEIU Local 585 - PA Department of Education - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - SEIU Local 585 - PSEA - Newspaper Clippings, Reports, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Pension - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Independent Coalition - Executive Meeting Minutes, Newsletters, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence with PA Governor Milton J. Shapp, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - PA AFL-CIO - Reports, Letters, Newsletters, Research Papers, 1971-1974 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - SEIU - School Memos, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - SEIU - Publication Department - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - SEIU - Scholarships - Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - SEIU - Misc. Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - SEIU - 26th Annual Wage Survey Report, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - SEIU - Pension Fund - National Industry Pension Fund Report, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - SEIU Local 585 - George Hardy Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - John Geagan International - George Fairchild Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - SEIU - T.E.A. Party Membership Forms, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Union Label & Service Trades Council - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Coalition of Labor Union Women - Letters, Newspaper Clippings, List of Delegates, 1974 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Gen. Membership and Exec. Board Meeting Minutes, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 2-3)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Election - Ballot Leaflets, Letters, List of SEIU Officers, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Newspaper Clippings - Strikes, Contract Negotiations, 1971-1973 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 585 - News Information - Newspaper Clippings, Letters, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - SEIU Local 585 - NOW - Letters, Pamphlets, Newsletters, 1973-1974 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Other Union Newspapers - Local 36 News, August, 1974 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Viewpoint Magazines, 1972-1973 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Election Ballots - Ballots, List of SEIU Members, Resolutions, 1972 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Monthly Audit Reports, 1972-1977 (Box 82, Folder 1-6)
  - Allegheny Valley School District - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Apollo-Ridge School District - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Apollo Ridge School District - Cafeteria - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Armstrong School District - Secretaries - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Armstrong School District - Custodians - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Armstrong School District - Cafeteria - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Armstrong County Health Center - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Armstrong School District - Teacher Aids - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Avella School District - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Avonworth School District - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Bethel Park School District - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Blair County - Valleyview Home - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Brownsville School District - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Churchill Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Connellsville Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Conway YMCA - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Cranberry Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Deer Lakes School District - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Allegheny County - Dues Check-Off, 1979-1980 (Box 84, Folder 1-3)
  - Albert Gallatin School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Building Services - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Burrell School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Butler County - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Butler County School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Butler County Parks and Recreation Committee - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 9)